gmatprepnow.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy | GMAT Prep Now

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for [www.GMATPrepNow.com](http://www.gmatprepnow.com/) (the "Site"). Isla Verde Education Inc, the provider of the Site (referred to as "Isla Verde Education Inc," "us" or "we"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. You acknowledge that by accessing or using our Site, you agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions of this Site ("Terms"). This Privacy Policy is part of such Terms. If you do not agree to the Terms, please do not access or use this Site.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by posting the revised Privacy Policy on this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Privacy Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

Please read the information below to learn more about our Privacy Policy:

**1.   What information do we collect from you?**

In order to better serve you, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering, submitting data or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and other personal identifying information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you go to next, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. An URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet.

**2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?**

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you (a) register for our services and register your e-mail address with us and/or (b) send e-mail messages, submit forms or transmit other information by telephone or letter.

We may also collect information from you at other points on our site that state that such information is being collected.

In addition, we may also collect certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. This information is ultimately stored in the form of store categories, and, in some cases, specific URLs. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our site and to gather demographic information.

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide services to you, or to allow our sponsors to provide services to you. We will also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, statistically analyze site use, and customize and improve our site's content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Site Terms of Use and this Private Policy.

**3\. With whom do we share your information?**

Through your use of the Site, you may have the opportunity to view, use or register for products or services offered by Company’s sponsors or other third parties. By creating an account and using the Site, you expressly consent to allow Company to share your email address with the party or parties providing such products or services. You agree that no further notice shall be required on the part of Company or any such third parties. You may withdraw your consent at any time by emailing us at [info@gmatprepnow.com](mailto:info@gmatprepnow.com)

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who illegally use our services and those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

**4\. How can you update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information?**

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information in your account online at any time by logging on to your account. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing us at: [info@gmatprepnow.com](mailto:info@gmatprepnow.com).  Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.

We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes.

**5\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?**

We may, from time to time, send you email regarding our services. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please email us at [info@gmatprepnow.com](mailto:info@gmatprepnow.com).

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies some parts of our site may not work properly in your case.

**6\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**

Your privacy is of utmost concern to us. Your Personally Identifiable Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Personally Identifiable Information is available through a password and unique username selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected Isla Verde Education Inc personnel have access to via password. We encrypt your Personally Identifiable Information and thereby prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to us.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

**7\. Do we use "cookies"?**

Yes.  A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow Web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may, however, prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

We may use third-party cookies as part of remarketing activities we conduct with Google and/or other third-party vendors, to help provide you with relevant messaging as you use the Internet. As part of these remarketing activities, these third-party cookies may record your visits to our Websites and web sites visited prior. Such cookies can then be used to serve targeted messaging to you on other websites. You may choose to be exempt from the use of Google remarketing cookies at the [Google advertising privacy page](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/#toc-optout). Alternatively, you may opt-out of remarketing on the Google network and similar networks at the[ Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) opt out page. Opting out will not prevent advertisements from being served to you on the Internet; it will only affect advertisements that utilize remarketing cookies to serve messaging on the specified networks. We are not responsible for the activities of other parties that may not comply with your opt-out requests.

**8\. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third party sites accessible from our site?**

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or anything else regarding this site, please contact us at: [info@gmatprepnow.com](mailto:info@gmatprepnow.com)

_Effective Date: March 1, 2011_
